[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the legislative branch of the federal government of the United States.", "correct_answer": "The Congress of the United States", "incorrect_answers": ["The Senate", "The Supreme Court", "The House of Representatives"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The largest burger weighed this much.", "correct_answer": "6,040 pounds (2,740 kg)", "incorrect_answers": ["6,878 pounds (3,120 kg)", "1,111 pounds (504 kg)", "18,388 pounds (8,341kg)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are many different theories of how the Milky Way galaxy was born.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the current heavyweight champion in Rocky Balboa, the sixth movie of the Rocky series?", "correct_answer": "Mason The Line Dixon", "incorrect_answers": ["Sydney The Snake Crawford", "Lewis Manifest Destiny Clark", "Tony The Tiger Sharp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Twinkies, the sponge cake with creamy filling, created by Hostess, have an indefinite shelf life.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first European child, born in the Western Hemisphere, was born in what would become this country/state.", "correct_answer": "Canada", "incorrect_answers": ["Cuba", "Virginia", "Barbados"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This author of popular novels, who was a lecturer at Wellesley College, spoke fluent  English, Russian and French and made chess problems in his spare time.", "correct_answer": "Nabokov", "incorrect_answers": ["Brecht", "Pasternak", "Steinbeck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was Tina Turner born?", "correct_answer": "26 November 1939", "incorrect_answers": ["19 November 1926", "1 November 1940", "30 November 1944"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the destination of the Air France Flight 447 that crashed on June 1, 2009 in the Atlantic Ocean?", "correct_answer": "Paris, France", "incorrect_answers": ["Los Angeles, California, USA", "Ottawa, Canada", "Rio de Janeiro, Brazil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following traps was dubbed the most infamous trap used in the Saw movies and involved the character named Amanda?", "correct_answer": "Reverse beartrap", "incorrect_answers": ["Rack trap", "Razor wire maze", "Flammable Jelly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is dolphins sense of hearing superior to that of humans?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Resident Evil: Apocalypse the only returning actors from the first movie were Mila Jovovich and Mike Epps.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]